(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-20T08:33:40.669767",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
体操いくよー！
Let's do some exercise!
からだ☆ダンダン　ダン！（GO！ GO！）
Body dandan, dan! (Go! Go!)
からだ冒険　出発進行！
Body adventure, departure!
さあ、海に潜るよー！
Now, let's dive into the sea!
カニさん　エビさん　コクコクコクコク！
Crabs, shrimps, stiff, stiff, stiff!
サメさん　サバさん　コクコクホネホネ！
Sharks, mackerels, stiff, bounce, bounce!
もっと潜ってみよう！
Let's dive deeper!
海藻体操　昆布にわかめ！
Seaweed exercise, kombu and wakame!
クリオネ　クリクリクリクリック！
Kurione, click, click, click, click!
海藻体操　でんでんダイコ！
Seaweed exercise, submarine dive!
クリオネ　クリクリクリック！クリック！
Kurione, click, click, click, click! Click!
さあ、海から出ちゃおう！
Now, let's come out of the sea!
着陸、恐竜になるよ！
Surfacing, becoming a dinosaur!
ガオー！
Roar!
こどもザウルス　どっしんどっしん！
Children'saurus, stomp, stomp!
こどもマンモス　ずっしんずっしん！
Child mammoth, thump, thump!
座って、おサルさんになるよ！
Sit down and become a little monkey!
ウホウホウホ！
Ooh, ooh, ooh!
グーグーパーパ　ルイジアン！
Gugu Papa, to Luigi's Garden!
グーグーパーパ　ゲンダイジウム！
Gugu Papa, to Gen-dai-ji!
立つよ！
Stand up!
ジュンジューン！
Junjun, go, go, go!
ニンジャのお散歩　そろーりそろーり！
Ninja's stroll, tip-toe, tip-toe!
いざとなったらアスリート！
Once you're set, you're an athlete!
走るよ！ついてきてね！
We're running! Come follow us!
じまんのエンジン　ジンジン燃やせ！
Rev up the engine, burn, burn, burn!
じまんのにんじん　どんどん食べて！
Eat up all those carrots! Nom, nom!
止まれよ！ピタッ！
Stop! Freeze!
ビューと風が吹いてきたよ！
Whoosh, a breeze has come along!
ラララスイスイ風に乗ろう！
Ride on that gentle breeze!
空を泳ごう！
Let's swim through the skies!
宇宙を覗こう！
Let's look out into space!
どんどん進む　地球のこどもだよ！
We are children of the Earth, moving ever onward!
ダイナモの音うねる坂道
The sound of the dynamo, the rolling hill,
だよ！ ゴー！
That's right! Go!
体だんだんだんだん
Move your body, step by step,
みんなでだんだんだんだん
Everyone, step by step,
体だんだん
Body, step by step,
ボケだらけ
Full of ditsy slips!
おー！
Oh!
ラプさんリモコン カラスは…
Lap-san's Remote: Crows are...
行きましょう！
Let's go!
はーい、パパ！
Yes, Papa!
ここじゃないです。
That's not it.
いや、そういう手だから。
Well, that's just the gimmick.
ええ…
Eh...
ラプさんリモコン、さ！
Lap-san's Remote: Sa!
言いましたよね、無駄遣いはしないでって。
I told you not to waste money.
財産はママが管理！じゃあパパはお財布持ってないの？
Mama manages the fortune! So Papa has no wallet?
聞いてます？
Are you listening?
もうパパもちょっとあれにハマっちゃってるからね。
Well, Papa got a bit hooked on that thing.
子供が知らなくてもいいことがこの世にはたくさんあるんだ。
There are many things children don't need to know.
ラプさんリモコン、し！
Lap-san's Remote: Shi!
死を…待つ…のみ…
Waiting... only for... death...
何？ 本当に何？
What? Seriously, what?
人間を含むこの世に存在するものは、いずれ滅びるとボクは思っているんだ。
Everything in this world will eventually perish, or so I believe.
てことだけど、分かった。
That's what I mean, understood?
わかった。
Understood.
あ、寝てた。
Ah, she fell asleep.
ふざけんな！
Don't mess with me!
ラプさんリモコン、す！
Lap-san's Remote: Su!
好きな食べ物が子供っぽいってだけで人を判断するな！
Don't judge people just because their favorite food is childish!
ハンバーグと唐揚げとオムライスとイチゴのショートケーキとコロッケ！
Hamburg steak, fried chicken, omurice, strawberry shortcake, croquettes!
おい、なんだ。笑ったのか？
Hey, what. Did you laugh?
この野郎、笑ったのか？
You bastard, did you laugh?
許さねぇ！
I won't forgive you!
ラプさんリモコン、せ！
Lap-san's Remote: Se!
世界征服！
World domination!
世界征服！ 世界征服！
World domination! World domination!
世界征服！世界征服！世界征服！世界征服！
World domination! World domination! World domination!
そのさ、世界征服ってさ、具体的に何やるの？
Also, what exactly do you do for world domination?
今ってところへんまで進んでるわけ？
How far along are you right now?
毎日遊んでるよね？ お父さんの仕事ってなんなの？
You play every day, right? What is Dad's job anyway?
黙れ！ パ、パパ？
Shut up! P-Papa?
世界を壊す 破壊神 誕生
The birth of the destruction god who destroys the world!
ラプラスさんに魔力…
Magic power on Laplus-san...
さあ…！
Now...!?
そんなのこの世に存在しないのだ！
That doesn't exist in this world!
そ、そうなのかな…！？
I-Is that so...!?
完
The End
ランダム・バイ・ランダム・ピックリだもん
Random by random, what a surprise!
生きてりゃ毎日大変 大問題のあとには楽しいことあるから
Life is hard every day, but fun follows big trouble!
ランダム・バイ・ランダム・叫んじゃえわ 試験だ毎日大変
Random by random, shout it out! Exams and daily hardships
大成功の種だぞ 笑えないじゃうんな笑え
They're seeds of great success, don't say you can't laugh!
ペコラン・ダ・ルルル・ルタ ペコラン・ダ・プッチャ・マイ・マインド
Pekoran da rururu ruta, Pekoran da put your mind
ノリノリ・の・しれん 星屑・快・爽快・ラ・ラ・ラ
Groove trial, stardust, pleasant, refreshing, la la la
ノリノリ・の・しれん 生・生・ラン・ダン ノリノリ・の・しれん 星屑・快・爽快・ラ・ラ・ラ
Groove trial, raw run dan, stardust, refreshing, la la la
受け取りひねるぞ
Receive and twist it!
届いて！心とちゃんと関係して、ワンダラ・ダ・ダン！
Reach them! Relate properly to the heart, wonder-da-dan!
誰か生まれ変わっ・カワイコド・ちゃんとキョタッテ、ワンダラ・ダ・ダン！
Someone reborn, cute child, stand at attention, wonder-da-dan!
さあフシよう ボクが言うんだもん 本当にするんだもん 現実超える未来
Come on, let's sing, I'll make it real, a future past reality!
ああ、百点も壁水滴でランチャ、ワンダラ・ダ・ダン！
Ah, even 100 points, splashing with wall water drops!
その街と・ヤセド・ワンダラ・ダ・ダン！
With that town and... wonder-da-dan!
楽しいも、おもしろがれること、探した前を、返事を聞かせてくれ
Fun things, things to enjoy, look ahead and reply!
身・緑の・ごちそう、体・極めつけて・一丁前
Body green feast, mastering the body to be first-class!
ワンダラ・ダ・ダン・発祥・ワンダラ・ダ・ダン、ワクワク全開
Wonder-da-dan origin, wonder-da-dan, excitement fully open!
みんな、ついてこれてるかな？
Everyone, are you keeping up?
大きな友達も、小さなお友達も、次は一緒に、手拍子で、行ってみよう！
Big and small friends, let's go together with clapping!
そっと 心の中で 熱い視線を作った
Quietly, in my heart, I made a passionate gaze.
振り向いてって 願いが ちょおっ てた
The wish for you to turn around was overflowing.
ヒーローイン・オーディション エントリーしたなら 私たちを 選んでくれるから
Heroine audition, if you entry, you'll choose us!
失礼しますが、RIP♡
Excuse me, but RIP♡
だから ごめん 失礼しますが 死んでください
So sorry, excuse me, but please die!
決めるベース ころ その 片方な 楽しい
Decide the base, roll, that, one-sided, fun!
デヴィッチ・マレ・エッヂ・オブ・フェ・カワイイ かわいいね
Devitch male edge of fe, cute, so cute!
神・神・者・世界・カ、リオペ、キミ・ウィズ・ザ・ベスト・ビギ・ダ・セ・オ・ラ・イ・エ・ス・ダケノ・アサ、ファイゴ
God, person, world, liope, best morning, figo!
角 生えて 事故で 犯罪じゃないから
Horns growing by accident, it's not a crime!
ダーティーの・ウサ・ミニチャ・ユラ・ソ・メイク・シュア・ヒューマン・ネイチャー
Dirty's usa minicha yura, make sure human nature!
さあ、みんな、人生について考える前に、この曲をつけて元気になろう！
Now everyone, before thinking about life, let's cheer up!
さあ、ほら、その場を上げて、みんなで…
Now, look, raise the mood, everyone together...
同じ未来を見ていたい あの夢手にしたい
I want to see the same future, I want to hold that dream in my hands.
それぞれ違った ココロで走れ go!
Running with our different hearts, go!
どこを見ても真っ暗な 場所に芽生えてた
Wherever I looked, in pitch-dark places, it sprouted.
ほんの小さな希望に この瞳奪われた
My eyes were stolen by just a tiny hope.
不安で揺れる 心を上手くチューニングして
Tuning my anxiously shaking heart just right,
ほんの小さな 勇気を出していたよ
I mustered up just a tiny bit of courage.
諦めの文字 デリートして進む
Deleting the word "give up," I move forward.
苦しいときも、もう私は ひとりじゃないから
Even when it's tough, I'm no longer alone,
だからもっと 夢追いかけたい ワクワク止まらない
so I want to chase my dreams even more, my excitement won't stop!
想像超えてく 世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a world that surpasses imagination.
アクセスしてみたい 後悔なんてそうさせない
I want to try accessing it, I won't let you have any regrets.
それぞれ違った ココロで走れ go!
Running with our different hearts, go!
仮想の空に輝く 眩しい想いは
The dazzling feelings shining in the virtual sky
見たことのない 光を現実に届けるよ
deliver an unseen light into reality.
いつも聞こえるエールは ここにキャプチャーして
Capturing the cheers I always hear right here,
また新しい 光を探したくなるよ
it makes me want to search for a new light.
君の笑顔は保存して進む
Saving your smile, I move forward.
悲しいときに見返すよ 力が湧くから
When I'm sad, I'll look back at it, because it gives me strength.
胸を張って 夢追いかけたい 奇跡の物語
Standing proud, I want to chase my dreams, a miraculous story.
一緒に作ろう 終わらない夢を
Let's create an endless dream together.
誰一人欠かせない 愛が舞い込んだ この世界
This world where love has fluttered in, where no one can be missed.
それぞれ違った ココロで彩れ
Color it with our different hearts!
よいこのみんな、かつもくせよ！
Good children, pay attention!
わがはいのお名前は、ラプラス・ダークネスだよ！
My name is Laplus Darknesss!
おねえさん、普段はお出かけとかあんまりしないんだけど、今日はとっても天気がいいからお散歩していこうか！
Normally, I don't go out much, but today the weather is so nice, so let's go for a walk!
桜の時期はちょっとすぎちゃったし、あじさいの季節もまだだけど、お花さんや動物さん、たくさん見つかるといいね！
The cherry blossom season has passed a bit, and it's not quite hydrangea season yet, but I hope we can find lots of flowers and animals!
長い…階段長い！
Long... these stairs are so long!
あ、お疲れ様！
Ah, good job!
公園の中はとっても広いんだけど、フラワー・トレインで楽々移動できちゃうみたい！
The park is huge, but it looks like we can travel easily on the Flower Train!
ここまでの坂道頑張ったのに、一瞬で追い越されちゃった…。
I worked so hard on the uphill slope up to here, but I got passed in an instant...
しばらく登ってきて、もうヘトヘト…。結構登ったと思うんだけど、頂上はまだかな？
I've been climbing for a while and I'm totally exhausted... I think I've climbed quite a bit, but is the summit still far?
おお、すごい！
Whoa, amazing!
おおーー！たかーい！こんな登ってきたんか！
Whoa! So high! Did I really climb this high?!
ここまで登ってきた疲れが一気に吹き飛ぶくらい、すっごい景色！町並みが手のひらに乗せられそうなぐらい小さく見える！
The view is so incredible that all the fatigue from climbing up here just blows away in an instant! The town looks so small it could fit right in the palm of my hand!
うらら うらら ぎゅっとしよう
Urarara, let's hold you tight
きっと だいじょうぶ
I'm sure it'll be alright
しゃがんで ジャンプだ こころ
Squat down and jump, let your heart
とびまわれ
fly around
うつむいて みたら
When I looked down,
あしが みえたよ
I could see my feet
かたい じめんを
I'll stomp hard
おもいっきり ふみこむぞ
onto the hard ground
かおを あげて (へんがおしよう)
Lift your face up (let's make a funny face)
せのびもして (あくびもしよう)
Stretch up high (let's yawn too)
ごきげんな ファンファーレ
A cheerful fanfare
うれしいな
I'm so happy
うらら うらら ぎゅっとしよう
Urarara, let's hold you tight
きっと できるよね
I'm sure we can do it
とびきりに なるぞ こころ
Our hearts will become extraordinary
大きく なれ
Grow big!
ハートぶるぶる いやなことに まけないぞ
My heart is trembling, I won't lose to bad things
たのしい かぜよ ふけ
Blow, happy wind!
うらら なみだもさ しあわせの たねだ
Urarara, even tears are the seeds of happiness
ぜんぶ やさしさに かえちゃうぞ
I'll turn everything into kindness
うらら うらら ぎゅっとしよう
Urarara, let's hold you tight
ずっと だいじょうぶ
It'll be alright forever
たのしく いけるさ こころ とびまわれ
We can go joyfully, heart, fly around
とびまわれ
Fly around!
つくろう えかきうた 始まるよ～！
Let's make and draw a song, it's starting!
あれ？って壊したん？ あれ？壊してない！
Huh? Did you break it? - Huh? I didn't break it!
ほら！がんばれ！がんばれ！
Come on! Do your best! Do your best!
これ押して！押したら夕ご飯ないよ！
Press this! If you press it, no dinner for you!
さっき打ち合わせしたでしょ！打ち合わせ！もう一回最初からやるよ！
We discussed this earlier during our meeting! Meeting! Let's do it over from the start!
やだ！やだ！やだ！だまって！だまって！だまって！
No! No! No! Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
いや、分かった分かった。よんちゃんもね、はいはい、かわいい。
No, I get it, I get it. Yon-chan too, yes yes, so cute.
違う！違う！違う！
No! No! No!
あのね、みんな、あの、私が、あの、「始まるよ」って言ったら、「うわー！」だからね、分かった？
Um, everyone, when I say "It's starting!", you say "Waaah!", okay? Got it?
次、え、な、なんでじゃないよ、さっきも言ったでしょ！いきますよー！
Next, wait, what do you mean? I said it earlier! Here we go!
つくろう えかきうた 始まるよー！
Let's make and draw a song, it's starting!
わあーーー！わあーーー！すごいねー！
Waaah! Waaah! That's amazing!
ということで、一人ずつ自己紹介できるかな？
With that said, can you each introduce yourselves?
はーい！沙花叉クロヱです！今日は…
Hi! I'm Sakamata Chloe! Today...
あ、どーも！
Ah, hello!
泣かないで！泣かないで、かなたちゃん大丈夫大丈夫、かなたちゃんのターンだから。
Don't cry! Kanata-chan, it's okay, it's Kanata-chan's turn.
がんばって、あ、にぎって、いぎた...
Do your best... Ah, grab it, I want to go...
あ、今日も握るんだ。はい、今日も頑張ってぎゅぎゅしていこうね。
Ah, you're gripping today too. Yes, let's do our best and grip tightly today.
がんばれ！わーい！はい、よろしくー！
Good luck! Yay! Yes, nice to meet you!
オレの名前はラプラス・ダークネスです。で、やめろや！
My name is Laplus Darknesss. And stop it!
やめろや！なかいいね、かなたちゃんと…え、ラプラスちゃんは仲いいのかな？
Stop it! You guys are close. Kanata-chan and... Eh, are Laplus-chan close?
仲良くない！やめなさいそういうのはね、みんな映ってるよ、映ってる。仲良くない。
We're not close! Stop saying things like that, everyone's on screen, you're on screen. We're not close.
オレのあさもきちゃんと結婚するの？
Are you marrying Asamoki-chan?
そうなの？なんかちょっと急コンされましたけど、じゃあ…
Is that so? We were suddenly matched, so...
やだ、やだじゃない！
No way! It's not 'no way'!
ちゃ、自己紹介できるかな？白上フブキです。結婚したくないです。
Can you introduce yourself? I'm Shirakami Fubuki. I don't want to get married.
ねえ、じゃあフブキちゃんは誰と結婚したいのかな？
Hey, then who does Fubuki-chan want to marry?
誰ともしたくないということですね。
That means you don't want to marry anyone.
ということで、ラプラスちゃんはちょっと振られたということで。
So, that means Laplus-chan got rejected.
すごいよ！やってるやってる！すごいよ！
Amazing! They're doing it! Amazing!
じゃあいろはちゃんお願いします。
Now, Iroha-chan, please.
はい、ござるです。こんにちは！いいこなんで、自己紹介がちゃんとできました。いろはねえさん、えらい！
Yes, it is Gozaru. Hello! Since I'm a good girl, I was able to introduce myself properly. Iroha-neesan, amazing!
えらい！一番えらい！はい、今日も頑張るでござる。
Amazing! The most amazing! Yes, I'll do my best today too.
ラプラスちゃんには負けません！よろしくお願い致します。対決だな。えらいえらい！
I won't lose to Laplus-chan! Best regards. It's a showdown. Amazing, amazing!
えらい、えらい、えらい、えらい！
Amazing, amazing, amazing, amazing!
はい、そして、みんな元気！たかねるいおねえさんだよ。
Yes, and everyone is energetic! It's Takane Lui-neesan.
はい、キッズども早く座ってください。誘導しますんで、はい、座って。
Yes, kids, please sit down quickly. I'll guide you, so yes, sit down.
もうしてるよ！してるからね、座り、座りなさい。
You're already doing it! You're doing it, so sit, sit down.
ということで、子供心を失っていないみんなに、今から絵描き歌で、誰が一番子供に近いかを勝負してもらうよ。
And so, we'll have everyone, who hasn't lost their childlike heart, compete using drawing songs to see who is closest to being a child.
みんな子供心を忘れてないよね？
You guys haven't forgotten your childlike hearts, right?
もちろん！大人です。見たところ、大人っぽい人いたけど大丈夫かな？もちろんもちろん！子供じゃないよね？大人じゃないよね？子供心を忘れてないっていうことで合ってるかな？
Of course! We're adults. Seeing that, there were people who looked adult-like, but will it be okay? Of course, of course! You're not children, right? You're not adults, right? Is it correct that you haven't forgotten your childlike hearts?
はい！大丈夫！みんな企画の趣旨分かってるね？
Yes! It's fine! Everyone understands the premise of the project, right?
企画の趣旨…しっかりだいふくのお絵描き歌でビジネス子供…じゃあみんな、ルールは簡単。
The premise of the project... drawing Daifuku's drawing song... business children... So everyone, the rules are simple.
お姉さんがお題を発表するから、一番子供っぽい絵描き歌を即興で作れた人が1ポイントもらえます。分かったかな？簡単でしょ？
Big sister will announce the topic, so whoever can improvise the most childlike drawing song gets 1 point. Understood? It's easy, right?
みんな準備はいいかな？はい！
Is everyone ready? Yes!
はい、ということで1つ目のお題は、こちら！ぞうさんです。みんなぞうさんかけるかな？
Yes, so the first topic is this! Zousan. Can everyone draw an elephant?
じゃあ、絵描き歌をみんなで考えていきましょう。シンキングタイム、スタート！
Well then, let's all think of a drawing song together. Thinking time, start!
みんなは…ぞうさん好きかな？
Do you guys like elephants?
これね、声で見つけたよ。
I found this by voice.
え、これ、ぞうさん見つけた？見けた。そう、お友達が滑り台だ。
Eh, did you find an elephant? I found it. Yeah, a friend is a slide.
あ、滑り台だね、それはね。
Ah, it's a slide, isn't it?
ぞうさんだ！ぞうさん、ぞうさん、ぞうさんだ！
It's an elephant! Elephant, elephant, it's an elephant!
ちょっと違うよ！ぞうさんだ！
That's a bit different! It's an elephant!
ケンカし…ケンカしちゃダメ。みんな仲良くね。みんな人のじゃなくて自分で考えるんだよ。
Don't fight... Don't fight. Everyone get along. Everyone, think for yourselves instead of copying others.
ということで、みんなかけたかな？
And so, has everyone drawn it?
じゃあ1人ずつ順番に発表してもらいたいと思います。一番、私、自信があるっていう人！
Now, I'd like everyone to present in turn. Who is the most confident?
じゃあちょっと、子供っぽくはい家えた人からさしていこうかな。先生先生、ありがとうございます！じゃあかなたちゃん1番で！
Then let's call on the person who answered like a child first. Teacher teacher, thank you! Well then, Kanata-chan is number one!
嬉しい！嬉しい、嬉しい！ということで、じゃあかなたちゃんのぞうさんの絵描き歌！
Happy! Happy, happy! So, Kanata-chan's elephant drawing song!
さあ、やっていきましょう！ミュージックスタート！
Let's get started! Music, start!
ぞうさん
Mr. Elephant,
お鼻が長いのね
you have such a long nose!
そうよ
Yes, I do.
母さんも長いのよ
My mom's nose is long, too!
ぞうさん
Mr. Elephant,
だれがすきなの
who do you like?
あのね
Well,
かあさんがすきなの
I like my mom!
しっぽもあるよ
I have a tail, too!
かなたちゃん絵描き歌やったことあるかな？
Have you ever done an illustration song, Kanata-chan?
ある！あるあるんだ！あるよね
I have! I have, I have! Right?
かなり下手
Pretty badly though.
すごい上手だったよ
It was really good!
上手だよ
It was good.
あれだね鼻から花水が出てるんだね
That's right, flower water is coming out of its nose.
そうだよ
That's right.
ここから出てんだよ
It's coming out right here.
とんだいや
Flying, no...
可愛いね
It's cute.
足の本数だって
And the number of legs...
足3本あるから
Since it has 3 legs...
もう1本どこやったのかな
Where did it put the other leg?
かなたちゃんよりうまくできるよっていう人いる？
Is anyone here who can do better than Kanata-chan?
じゃあちょっとやりやってた
Then let's look at...
ラプラスちゃんの見ていこうかな
Laplus-chan's drawing.
スタート
Start!
ぞうさん
Mr. Elephant,
おっきいチョウチョ
you're a big butterfly!
三角丸々
Triangle, circle, circle,
足足足足しっぽ
leg, leg, leg, leg, tail,
完成！
All done!
いいでしょ、見て
Isn't it good? Look!
やった、絵描き歌でね足のところは足足足足って言うのね
Yeah, in the illustration song, for the legs it says leg, leg, leg, leg...
すごい斬新だったね、ラプラスちゃん
It was super original, Laplus-chan.
耳のシワのディテールがポイント
The detail of the ear wrinkles is the point.
え、が、ヒップホップなの？
Eh, is it hip hop?
ヒップホップ絵描き歌
Hip hop illustration song.
最近のかなたちゃんのほうがまだ絵描き歌っぽかったかな
Kanata-chan's recent one was more like an illustration song.
見て、これ
Look at this.
足足足足がちょっとね
The leg, leg, leg, leg was a bit...
びっくりしちゃったけど
I was surprised, but...
耳のディテールがさ、めっちゃ大きくて
The ear detail was, like, super big.
私の方がうまいよって人
Is anyone here who can do better than me?
じゃあ元気がいい風紀ちゃん行ってみようかな
Then let's try energetic Fubuki-chan.
一番うまくかけるよ
I'm going to draw it the best.
スタート
Start!
ぞうさん
Mr. Elephant,
お耳がふたつ
you have two ears,
にょきにょきにょきにょきお尻からちょろり
growing out, peeking from your bottom,
おトマトふたつとちょんちょんちょんぞうさん
two tomatoes and dot-dot-dot, Mr. Elephant,
わあ、ぞうさん！
Wow, Mr. Elephant!
一番ぞうさんみたい
Looks most like an elephant.
これは上手でしょう
This is good, right?
ちゃんと耳がふたつあるんだね
It properly has two ears.
アピールしないの
Don't appeal so much.
みんなたちのターンは終わった
Everyone's turn is over.
終わったよ
It's over.
いや、うまい風紀ちゃん
Man, you're good, Fubuki-chan.
ラスト、いろはちゃんやってみる？
Last, want to try, Iroha-chan?
分かった！うまく描けるかな
Understood! Wonder if I can draw it well.
絵描き歌かけなきゃ、ゾウさんもかけるよね、いろはちゃんもね。
If we do the drawing song, we can draw elephants too, right Iroha-chan?
かける。ゾウさん知ってる。
I can. I know elephants.
頭なでられてます。
My head is being petted.
忍者（ラプラス）はゾウさん知らないよ。
Ninja (Laplus) doesn't know elephants.
書けるよ！
I can draw it!
忍者なの？
Are you a ninja?
だって私ゾウさん乗ったことあるからわかるよ！ラプラスゾウさん見たことあるからわかるし！
Because I've ridden an elephant before so I know! Laplus has seen one before so she knows!
しかも乗ったことあるもん！
Plus I've actually ridden one!
乗ったことある！
You've ridden one?
あぶない！
Watch out!
はい、じゃあいろはちゃんのゾウさんの絵描き歌、スタート！
Alright, then Iroha-chan's elephant drawing song, start!
長い筑紫後と 四つのちょんちょこりん
A long Tsukushi and four chon-chokorin,
上が大きいおもち
the top is a big mochi,
ちょんでしっぽが生えたなら
and if a tail sprouts out,
逆向きのカマボコつけて 丸とちょんちょんちょん、ゾウさん！
attach a reversed kamaboko and maru, chon-chon-chon, an elephant!
おおすごい！
Oh, amazing!
こないだ公園で見たゾウさん見て、え、ぜんぜん見て。
Look at the elephant we saw at the park recently. Eh, look at it.
なんか、あの、一番中、ポカったよ。
Somehow, um, the innermost one messed up.
こないだ。ちょっとポカった。ちょっとポカった。
The other day. Kind of messed up. Kind of messed up.
絵描き歌だから、ふんわりしてもちょっと絵描き歌だからちょっとふんわりしても
It's a drawing song, so even if it's fluffy... Even if it's a bit fluffy because it's a drawing song.
全然違うよ！すごいアピールしてる。
It's totally different! You're really appealing it.
この中で一番子供心があった人にね、ワンポイントあげたいと思います。
In this group, I'd like to give one point to whoever had the most childlike heart.
ほら、大空ちゃ、見て見て。みんなめちゃめちゃ横向いてるの。
Look, Oozora-cha, look look. Everyone is facing sideways.
ええ、戦ったゾウさんこれ。
Eeeh, this is an elephant that fought.
じゃあ子供っぽい、子供心を残していた人は、
So the person who kept their childlike heart is...
ふぶきちゃん！
Fubuki-chan!
だからね、子供らしい言葉選びでね、絵描き歌をしていたなということで、
So, she chose childlike words to do the drawing song,
ふぶきちゃんちょっと空気。
Fubuki-chan, the air is...
あ、王冠つけたんだ！WINって書いてね。WIN！おしゃれ！
Ah, you added a crown! You wrote WIN. WIN! Stylish!
それじゃあ みんな二つ目のお題は
So everyone, the second topic is...
こちら！
Right here!
カラス！
A crow!
カラスじゃーん！
It's a crow!
なんかきたね、カラスさんが来ました。
Looks like something arrived. A crow is here.
みんなカラス、このカラス描けるかな？
Everyone, a crow. Can you draw this crow?
可愛いカラスちゃん描いてください。
Please draw a cute crow-chan.
ラプラスちゃんはカラス描けるよね、もちろん。
Laplus-chan can draw a crow, of course.
うん、だっていつも一緒でしょ？
Yeah, because we're always together, right?
あ、いつも一緒？
Ah, always together?
うん。
Yeah.
え、じゃあそれってラプラスのダークネスなんじゃないの？
Eh, then isn't that Laplus Darkness itself?
え、ラプラスちゃんなの？この子が。
Eh, is it Laplus-chan? This kid.
え、確かに！言われてみればね、カラス、そっくりよ。
Eh, true! Now that you mention it, it looks just like a crow.
誰やねん！やばい、怒られる。
Who are you?! Oh no, I'm gonna get yelled at.
じゃあ行くよ、みんな。カラスこれ見本見ながら。
Then let's go, everyone. Looking at this crow as a reference...
それでは、シンキングタイム スタート！
Now then, thinking time, start!
カラス カラス カラス カラス
Crow, crow, crow, crow...
全然カラスじゃない 全然カラスじゃん
That's totally not a crow, that totally is a crow.
あのね、いろはちゃんがカラスのマネうまいよ。
Um, Iroha-chan is really good at imitating crows.
あ、やってくれる？
Oh, will you do it?
うん、じゃあやるよ。やってくれるの？
Yeah, then I'll do it. You will?
嘘嘘でした！嘘嘘でした！
Just kidding, just kidding!
みんな描けたかな？
Did everyone finish drawing?
描けた！私めちゃめちゃ描けてる、ラプラスに。
Drawn! I drew a lot, Laplus.
一番自信があるよっていう人！
Anyone who has the most confidence!
ええー！ちょこ先輩はちょっとあんまり恥ずかしい？
Eeeh! Choco-senpai is a bit too shy?
誰が一番上手かな？先生！見せてほしい、にゃん。
Who is the best? Teacher! I want to see, Nyan.
はい、ちょっと、ごめんね、ごめんね。すごい遠くて聞こえなくて、ごめんね。とにかく聞こえなかった。
Yes, wait, sorry, sorry. It was so far away I couldn't hear, sorry. I couldn't hear at all.
何て言った？「欲しいでござる、にゃん」？
What did you say? 'I want it for desu-garu, nyan'?
はい、じゃあラプラスちゃんからいくのかな？
Yes, so shall we start from Laplus-chan?
では、え、ラプラスちゃんのカラスの...
Then, um, Laplus-chan's crow...
おえかきうた、スタート！
Drawing song, start!
えい、せーの！
Hey, ready, go!
ん？なんか違うな、作っちゃお！
Huh? That's not right, let's make one!
やーね、やーね、
Right, right,
反対のやーね。
the opposite right.
大きく山と見せかけてディグダ？
Making it look like a big mountain, but it's Diglett?
違った！錯覚、錯覚！
Wrong! Optical illusion!
丸書いて、ぽーん！
Draw a circle, boom!
はっと！これでからす…はっと！
Aha! With this, it's a crow... Aha!
違う！
No!
結構カオスだよ！
It's pretty chaotic!
ニワトリだね！
It's a chicken!
ええ？違います！
Eh? No!
私が描いてくれたのかな？
Did you draw this for me?
ちょっと比べてみようか。
Let's compare them a bit.
違う！横向きにして…
No! Turn it sideways...
ほらほらほら！鳴いてるよ！鳴いてるよ！
Look, look, look! It's crying!
いやでもね、でもね、でもね、リズム感はよかったでしょ！
No, but, but, but, the rhythm was good, right?!
いいでしょ。
Right?
ニワトリを描いたということです！
That means I drew a chicken!
カラスじゃなくて、じゃあラプラスのニワトリよりも上手にカラスかけるよって人、
Instead of a crow, anyone who thinks they can draw a crow better than Laplus's chicken,
吹雪ちゃんが急にね、急に自信がついてきたので、吹雪ちゃんにお願いしようかな？
Fubuki-chan suddenly gained confidence, so I should ask Fubuki-chan, right?
さっきとね、上げる手の位置が全然違かったね。
The position of the raised hand was completely different from earlier.
だってさ、あそこ見てさ、そこ見たから…手、引いちゃったからね。
Because, you know, looking there, seeing that... because I pulled my hand back.
だから、そこ見た。だから、そこ見た。
That's why I looked there.
じゃあ吹雪ちゃん、準備はいいかな？はい、いきます！
Well Fubuki-chan, are you ready? Okay, here we go!
吹雪ちゃんのカラスのおえかきうた、スタート！
Fubuki-chan's crow drawing song, start!
とんねる一つ、
One tunnel,
お山ににょきにょき。
sprouting up on the mountain.
木が3本？おなにこれ、三角？
Three trees? Oh, what is this, a triangle?
たまごじゃない、たぬきは、たぬきは、にちょ、にちょ。
Not an egg, a raccoon dog, two, two.
ばさばさ、つばさ、つばさ、つばさ。
Flap flap, wings, wings, wings.
くちばし、ざざんクロス。
Beak, Zazan cross.
ちょ…ちょっと待って名前が…カラス！
Wh... wait, the name is... crow!
おお！えっ、えっ、待って、上手！えっ、待って！
Oh! Eh, eh, wait, good! Eh, wait!
サザンクロスでちょっとね、びっくりしちゃったけどさ！
I was a bit surprised by the Southern Cross!
待って待って、ほら見て、クオリティ高いね！
Wait wait, look, high quality!
かっこいい！
Cool!
え、やっぱね、ふぶきちゃんのおえかきうたかっこよかったね、サザンクロスかね？
Eh, as expected, Fubuki-chan's drawing song was cool, was it the Southern Cross?
ざざんクロスで…お姉さんにハマる、ハマっちゃってさ、なんというか、だいぶ爆笑しちゃいそうだったけれども堪えましたということで。
With the Zazan cross... I got hooked on it, so to speak, I was about to burst out laughing, but I held it in.
ふぶきちゃんより子供っぽくできるよって人。
Anyone who can do it more child-like than Fubuki-chan.
あー、なんか、散らかされてますけど大丈夫？あ、そんたくがありましたね。
Ah, somehow, it's a mess, but is it okay? Ah, there was favoritism.
じゃあいろはちゃん、いけるかな？
Well Iroha-chan, can you do it?
見ててね！いくよ！
Watch me! Here I go!
いろはちゃんのカラスのおえかきうたまで、3、2、1、スタート！
Until Iroha-chan's crow drawing song, three, two, one, start!
大きき鏡もち見つけてるの、
Finding a big kagami-mochi,
お弁当の中に入ってるやつ。
the one inside the bento box.
頭に生やしてトランプのダイヤのマークとか、かまぼこのかまぼこが2つ。
Sprouting on the head, like a diamond mark from playing cards, or two kamaboko fish cakes.
お目々は大きいて、2つのお羽がばさばさばさ、真ん中に大きな手裏剣書いたら完成、からす！
Big eyes, two wings flap flap flap, draw a big shuriken in the middle and it's complete, a crow!
ほらできた！米いろはちゃんすごい、もう、後ろの子がね、めちゃくちゃ踊っててもう、いろはちゃんの歌が頭に入ってこなかったけど
Look, it's done! Kome Iroha-chan is amazing, the kid in the back was dancing so much that I couldn't get Iroha-chan's song into my head, but
できて、できて、できて、できてるけど、2じゃないよ！
It's done, done, done, it's done, but it's not 2!
なんだろ、クオリティが高い子たちが爆弾魔がいたんだよ。
I wonder, there were high-quality kids, there was a bomber.
爆弾魔、爆発しましたよ。
The bomber exploded.
あなた！
You!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
らぷらすと いっしょだよ！
We're together with Laplus!
もうね！
Yeah!
えーっとね、その中の部分なんか、かなたちゃんのね、
Um, that inner part kind of... Kanata-chan's...
あの手裏剣みたいに見えてきちゃったんだけど、頭に刺さってる！
started looking like a shuriken, but it's stuck in her head!
これが答えだ！
This is the answer!
ほら見てほら見て！合ってる合ってる、
Look, look! It's right, it's right,
合ってる合ってる！
it's totally right!
じゃあ、かなたちゃん、準備はいいかな？
So Kanata-chan, are you ready?
はい、かなたちゃんのカラス、絵描き歌っていきましょう！
Okay, let's do Kanata-chan's crow drawing song!
スタート！
Start!
まあるい目ん子、目ん子、
Round little eyes, little eyes,
海だ、海だ、空のはず、
it's the sea, the sea, supposed to be the sky,
わかんないか、落ちてるね、
I don't know, it's falling down,
隣にどんぶり、
Next to a rice bowl,
next to a rice bowl,
仲良く、吉野家の、
get along, at Yoshinoya's,
なんとは分からない、
who knows what it is,
ちょっと可愛い感じに、
in a somewhat cute style,
ちっちゃお、お、お、ね、目ができてきた、
little, oh, oh, hey, eyes are forming,
ここで...
right here...
終わっちゃうよ！
It's ending!
びゃらむ、つけたら、できる、ここの、三、五、
If you add the whiskers, you can make the... 3, 5,
海の、山を、キラキラ、光る、キラキラ、ひっ...
ocean's mountain, shining, sparkling, shi...
できたよ、チョコボ！
It's done, a Chocobo!
チョコボだね、それはね。カラスじゃないね。
That's a Chocobo, isn't it? Not a crow.
チョコボだ！チョコボだ！すごい！チョコボ、
It's a Chocobo! Amazing, a Chocobo!
歌が、違くなっちゃうね、それね。
The song turned out different, didn't it?
4匹の中ではチョコボが強いみたいだったけど、子供心を残していた人は...
Among the four, the Chocobo seemed strongest, but the one who kept their childlike heart...
いろはちゃん！
is Iroha-chan!
まさかの！
No way!
まさかの、最弱じゃあ、
Seriously, the weakest?
全部のお題が終わったのね。
All the prompts are finished now.
もうベストオブ子供心を決めたいと思います。
Now we'll decide the Best Childlike Heart.
チームできてますか？
Are the teams ready?
はい、終わって。
Yes, we're done.
はい、ということで、一番子供心があった子は...
Alright, so, the one with the most childlike heart is...
誰かなー？誰かなー？誰かなー？
Who could it be? Who could it be?
ラプラスちゃん以外で！
Aside from Laplus-chan!
おめでとう！おかしい、おかしい、おかしい！
Congratulations! That's weird, weird, weird!
素晴らしい！これはね、ちょっと褒美ががありまして、
Wonderful! As a reward for this,
ルイお姉さんにめいっぱい甘えさせてもらう権利を獲得してしまい...
you've earned the right to be thoroughly pampered by Lui-neesan!
このあとね、じゃあ、私のうちでね、ご飯食べようね。
After this, let's go eat at my place.
みんなの大好きな、何食べたい？何食べたい？
Everyone's favorite, what do you want to eat?
ハンバーグ！ハンバーグだね！
Hamburg steak! Hamburg steak, right?
ハンバーグ食べよー！
Let's eat Hamburg steak!
みんなでハンバーグ食べよ！
Let's all eat Hamburg steak together!
いいですか？えっと、
Is that good? Um,
逆に子供から最も遠かったのは、
conversely, the one furthest from childhood was...
ラプラスちゃんです！おめでとう！
Laplus-chan! Congratulations!
お疲れ様でした！すごいです！
Good job! Amazing!
涙目でございます。
She's on the verge of tears.
ラプラス、本当に、あの、今日ね、頑張っていらっしゃいました、本当にお疲れ様です！
Laplus, you really worked hard today, truly great job!
そしてあなたに、おしおきがあります。
And now, you have a punishment.
おしおき？
A punishment?
おしおきの内容は、はい、ルイお姉さんに踏まれるです！
The punishment is, yes, being stepped on by Lui-neesan!
それはいいですよ！
That's fine by me!
ちょっと、それはいいぞ。じゃあ、みんなで踏もうか！
Wait, that's good. Shall we all step on her together?
いやいや、ちょっと待って！みんなで踏むのは違うでしょ！
No no, wait! Stepping on her together is wrong!
ルイだけですよ！
Only Lui!
踏み込めませんてんちょー！あ、じゃあちょっと目つぶって待っててもらっていいかな？
I can't step on her, manager! Ah, then can you close your eyes and wait?
うそ、ほっちぷれいってこと？
No way, is this unattended play?
目つぶって、じゃあ踏むね。
Close your eyes, then I'll step on you.
踏むの嫌いじゃないですけどね、そういうのはい。
It's not that I dislike being stepped on, but yeah.
じゃあ行きますよ！ちょっと今順番決めてるからね。
Here we go! We're just deciding the order now.
全員、あ、こういうのも別に嫌いじゃないんで、はい、待ってますよ。
Everyone... well, I don't dislike this sort of thing either, so yeah, I'm waiting.
じゃあ、みんな、お別れの挨拶。せーの、ばいばーい！
Alright everyone, parting greetings. Ready, bye-bye!
うそでしょ。一番のおしおきじゃん、それは！
No way. That's the ultimate punishment!
シャキーン パワワっ！
Sha-kin! Pawawa!
ぱら ら ぱわわ あっぷ ぱわわぁ
Para ra pawawa up pawawa~
ぱら ら ぱわわ あっぷ ぱわぱ
Para ra pawawa up pawapa
ぱら ら ぱわわ あっぷ ぱわわぁ
Para ra pawawa up pawawa~
おひさまがのぼるパワー
Power of the rising sun
たったかー
Tattaka~
おひさまがのぼるパワー
Power of the rising sun
たったかー
Tattaka~
今すぐ走り出そうよ うさかめ
Let's run right now, Usakame!
うさかめ！
Usakame!
とったか じゃんけん ぽんっ！
Rock, paper, scissors, pon!
転んで チョキチョキだって
Even if I fall, doing choki-choki,
パワパワ パワパワ アップアップアップ
Power power, power power, up up up!
顔洗うよ 顔洗って
Wash my face, wash my face,
僕の手のひらを膝まわりに見せて
Show the palms of my hands around my knees,
パワパワ パワパワ パワー
Power power, power power, power!
歯磨き！ 歯磨き嬉しいパン！
Brushing teeth! Brushing teeth happily, pan!
元気だパワー ピキピキ楽しいパワー
Energetic power, piki-piki fun power,
お日様パワー いってきまーす！
Sunshine power, I'm off!
ピヨピヨピヨピヨ…
Piyo piyo piyo piyo...
ピキピキ 小さなパワー
Piki-piki, small power,
大きなパワー 浮き浮きパワー
Big power, uki-uki power,
ぞうさんパワー ぞうさんパワー
Elephant power, elephant power,
青い空へ高くジャンプだ！
Jump high up into the blue sky!
パワパワ パワパワ アップアップアップ
Power power, power power, up up up,
お日様パワー いってきまーす！
Sunshine power, I'm off!
行ってきまーす！
I'm off!
ピヨピヨピヨピヨ…
Piyo piyo piyo piyo...
ピキピキ ちっちゃなパワー わわ！
Piki-piki, tiny power, wawa!
大きなパワー わわ！
Big power, wawa!
ウキウキパワー わわ！
Uki-uki power, wawa!
ぞうさんパワー わわ！
Elephant power, wawa!
青い空へ高くジャンプだ！
Jump high up into the blue sky!
パワパワ パワパワ パワパワパワー
Power power, power power, power power power!
ピキピキ パワパワ パワパワパワー
Piki-piki power power, power power power!
パワパワ パワパワ パワパワパワー
Power power, power power, power power power!
ウキウキ パワパワ パワパワパワー
Uki-uki power power, power power power!
パワパワ パワパワ パワパワパワー 楽しいパワー
Power power, power power, power power power, fun power!
楽しいパワー
Fun power!
楽しいパワー パワパワパワー
Fun power, power power power!
ぐうだって チョキチョキだって パーだって パワパワパワー じゃんけんぽん！
Guu, choki, pa, power power power, rock-paper-scissors, pon!
誰だ 誰だ 誰だ 誰だ パワパワパワー
Who is it? Who is it? Who is it? Who is it? Power power power!
パワパワ パワパワ パワパワパワー
Power power, power power, power power power!
大きな声で パワパワパワー
With a loud voice, power power power!
パワパワ パワパワ パワパワパワー
Power power, power power, power power power!
元気な声で パワパワ パワパワ パワパワパワー
With an energetic voice, power power power!
幸せ パワパワ パワパワパワー わあ！
Happiness, power power power, wah!
ろくさん、こんにちは。
Hello, Roku-san.
今日はね、お姉さんがね、いいものを見せてあげちゃうよ。
Today, big sis is going to show you something nice.
お母さんには内緒かもね。
It might be a secret from your mom.
これ見て！「ラプラス・ダークネス 誕生日記念グッズ」って書いてあるね！知ってるかな？
Look at this! It says "La+ Darknesss Birthday Commemoration Goods"! Do you know it?
いや、知らなくてもいいんだけどさ、見てってよ。あのさ、アクリルスタンドって言うんだけど、知ってる？
Well, you don't have to know, but check it out. It's called an acrylic stand, do you know it?
なんか、うすっぺらい板。
It's like a flat plate.
食べちゃダメだよ。
You mustn't eat it.
ほら、かわいいね、イラストが。
Look, the illustration is so cute.
次、これ。「ラプラスパペット」。
Next, this. The "La+ Puppet".
これぬいぐるみだね。あ、でも普通のぬいぐるみじゃないんだよ、これ。
It's a stuffed toy. Ah, but it's not just any ordinary stuffed toy.
こうやってこうやって手にめるとね、しゃべらせられるんだよね。
If you put your hand in it like this, you can make it talk.
ラプラス・ダークネスに好きなことを言わせられるって（笑）変な使い方しちゃダメだよ。
You can make La+ Darknesss say whatever you like. Don't use it weirdly.
お母さんに言っといてね。
Tell your mom about it.
お兄ちゃんにも言っといて。
Tell your big brother too.
最後これ。「おしゃべり型スマホリング」。
Lastly, this. The "Chattering Smartphone Ring".
スマホ持ってるかな、ろくさーん？
Do you have a smartphone, Roku-san?
ええ！？
What?!
その歳で持ってるの！？
You have one at that age?!
変な使い方しちゃダメだよ！
Don't use it weirdly!
これ全部、このグッズ全部入ったフルセットっていうのがあってね、これを購入してくれた人にはですね、特典が二つついてきちゃうらしい。
There's a full set containing all these goods, and for those who purchase it, it seems two special bonuses come with it.
二つって特典て分かるかな？
Do you understand what two bonuses means?
難しいこと使っちゃったね。うん。
I used a difficult word, didn't I? Yeah.
なんかね、おまけ、おまけだよ。ラムネのお菓子みたいなさ、そんな感じのやつね。
It's like an extra, a freebie. Like ramune candy, something like that.
1つ目は、ラプラス・ダークネス箱押し複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカード！長いね特典の名前が。分かったかな？
First is the La+ Darknesss foil-stamped duplicate autographed cheki-style bromide card! That's a long bonus name. Did you get that?
まあラプラス・ダークネスさんのね、そのね複製サインっていうね、なんか、そういっぱいサインが入ったブロマイドカードがもらえるわけですね。
Well, you get a bromide card with lots of duplicate signatures from La+ Darknesss-san.
いらない？そんなこと言わないの。
You don't want it? Don't say that.
ちょっと星が、欲しがるよそら。
You'll want it, come on.
お母さんに言っといて。「ほしい」つって。
Tell your mom, "I want it."
ぽいす！らぷらすといっしょ
Pois! Together with Laplus!
ね、これちょっと...、ちょっとね、
Hey, this is a bit... a bit, you know—
いかがわしいんじゃない、いかがわしいボイスなんじゃないって思うよね？
You'd think, "Isn't this a bit lewd? Isn't it a lewd voice?" right?
全然違います。
It's totally different.
全然普通のね、あの、ボイスなんでね。
It's a completely normal, you know, voice.
ちょっと詳しい内容はちょっと言えないんですけど、
I can't go into too many details, but...
まあちょっとね、ホロクサー、君がね、え、ちょっといい感じにラプラスさんとね、かがわられちゃう、かがわられちゃう...
Well, you know, Holoxer, you... get all cozy with Laplus-sama and get all hooked up—
っていうボイスですね。
It's a voice like that.
聴きたい。ね、聴きたいよね？
I want to hear it. Right, you want to hear it too?
そう、買って買って買って買って。はい。
That's right, buy it, buy it, buy it, buy it. Yes.
分かったかな？はい、以上。商品紹介でした。
Did you get that? Okay, that's all. That was the merchandise introduction.
世界はとっても広いから
Because the world is so vast,
夢は大きい方がいい
It's better to have big dreams.
夢に向かって
Heading towards your dreams,
ラプラさんリモコン！ おーそらーい
Rapla-san Remote! Up in the sky—
さあ 元気に行くよ！
Now, let's go with energy!
ハレ ハレ ハレ
Hare, hare, hare,
きっとハレる 明日も会える
Surely it'll clear up, we can meet tomorrow too.
ハレ ハレ ハレ
Hare, hare, hare,
きっとハレる 明日も会える
Surely it'll clear up, we can meet tomorrow too.
そろそろ おしまい
It's almost time to wrap up.
トンネルのむこうは
Beyond the tunnel
青空いーっぱい
Is a boundless blue sky.
今日も手を広げて 世界が待っている
Spread your arms wide today, the world is waiting.
じゃあみんな バイバーイ！またねー！
Well then everyone, bye-bye! See you later!